YUPING WANG

Mobile	+86 18616956116	Mail	sevenbamboos@gmail.com
Git	github.com/sevenbamboos	Blog	sevenbamboos.github.io/my-blog
Address	75 Archmillen Ave, Pakuranga, Auckland		

PROFILE1

15 years of detailed-oriented software programming; 6 years of Scrum master practices (TeamForge and Jira).

Strong understanding of object-oriented design and functional programming. Extensive experience in large-scale software trouble-shooting.

Solid knowledge and broad interests in JavaEE: JBoss, Hibernate, Spring; WEB development: Angular, React; and a wide range of technical stacks: C#, <u>ASP.NET</u> MVC, Entity framework, TPL DataFlow, Scala, Akka, R, NumPy, SciPy, Git, Subversion, Oracle, Jenkins.

EXPERIENCE

TEAM LEADER	AGFA HEALTHCARE (SHANGHAI) CO., LTD.	2010-2017
-------------	--------------------------------------	-----------

Contributor and maintainer of connectivity module of Enterprise Imaging information system (JavaEE, Angular, Jenkins). Scrum master of development team with 5-6 software engineers. Workload: coding (60%); component design (20%); source code review (20%)

SENIOR SOFTWARE	KODAK SHANGHAI PRODUCT	2006-2010
ENGINEER	DEVELOPMENT CENTER	

Developer of Advertisement player module (Java); Web developer of Kodak Digital Cinema System (JSP, Servlet, Javascript)

SOFTWARE	SHANGHAI INTERNATIONAL COMMODITY	2002-2006
ENGINEER	AUCTION CO., LTD.	

Developer of information system (JavaEE); Developer of online auction platform for private car license of Shanghai (JSP, Servlet)

-

¹ Last update on 2018/01/06

EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS²

FREE CODE CAMP'S FRONT EN	2016	
IELTS (ACADEMIC) OVERALL B	2016	
SUN CERTIFICATED JAVA PRO	2001	
EAST CHINA NORMAL UNIVERSITY, SHANGHAI	MASTER OF SOFTWARE ENGINEERING	2003-2006
SHANGHAI UNIVERSITY OF ELECTRIC POWER	BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE	1997-2001

REFERENCES

Stephen Yu	Agfa HealthCare IT (Shanghai), General Manager	T +86 21 2412 2003 M +86 15026585382
Shijie Wan, Ph.D	Kodak Shanghai Product Development Center, General Manager	T +86 21 5884 1818
Carrie Dailor	Lead QA tester for the Kodak Digital Cinema Services	cdailor@yahoo.com
Lin Yuan	Shanghai International Commodity Auction CO., LTD.	T +86 21 33661456

 $^{{}^2} Free\ Code\ Camp's\ Certification:\ https://www.freecodecamp.org/sevenbamboos/front-end-certification$